Calendar Girls meets The Full Monty
12 Men of Christmas is a comedy, romance, tv movie
film directed by Arlene Sanford.
A high-powered New York publicist finds herself in Montana promoting a
charity calendar after being betrayed by her boss and fiancé.
Unfortunately, matters of the heart are just as complicated
in the wilds as they are in the big city.
E.J. Baxter, played by Kristin Chenoweth.
Will Albrecht, played by Josh Hopkins.
Jan Lucas, played by Anna Chlumsky.
Roz Baxter, played by Erin Dilly.
Jason Farrar, played by Stephen Huszar.
Lillah Sherwood, played by Heather Hanson.
12 Men of Christmas is a 2009 American romantic comedy television
film made for the Lifetime Television network.
Directed by Arlene Sanford and starring Kristin Chenoweth,
the film is based on the novel Dating Mr.
December by Phillipa Ashley with the teleplay adaptation written by Jon Maas.
Anna Chlumsky, Aaron Abrams, Stephen Huszar, and Peter Mooney also star.
The film had its world premiere on Lifetime on December 5, 2009.
The story takes place in Kalispell, Montana, United States, but
the film was shot in Calgary, Alberta, Canada.
It tells the story of a New York publicist who takes
a job in a small town in Montana.
The reference to 12 men in the title refers to members of the volunteer Kalispell Search and Rescue
team who are the first point of rescue for those in danger at Glacier National Park.
The film explores themes of holiday, montana, rocky
mountains, calendar, woman director.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.